[{"answer": "It told me something was really wrong.", "docId": "130826pmt", "aSentId": 56, "question": "Now when you saw the car, what did it tell you about what may have happened here?", "qSentId": 55}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, he's a tough kid, he's in great shape, and he's really smart, but I'm afraid that he's not geared up for this environment.", "docId": "130826pmt", "aSentId": 68, "question": "Do you think he has it in him to keep safe in an environment, in the one that he's in now?", "qSentId": 67}, {"answer": "I would say, hey, we all make mistakes and it doesn't matter how far out you are, or what's happened, we want you to come home.", "docId": "130826pmt", "aSentId": 81, "question": "What would you like to say to him?", "qSentId": 80}, {"answer": "Yes, those memories never die, of course, and we wanted to just talk to Mr. Croom.", "docId": "130826pmt", "aSentId": 97, "question": "When you hear a story like the one I've just described about Jonathan Croom, and you see the anguish of his farther, it must bring back very vivid memories for both of you?", "qSentId": 96}, {"answer": ".", "docId": "130826pmt", "aSentId": 128, "question": "And what do you say to youngsters who want to follow him -- in Christopher's footsteps like that?", "qSentId": 127}, {"answer": "Well, you know, it really depends on what you start with in terms of your physical health and what resources you have.", "docId": "130826pmt", "aSentId": 149, "question": "Realistically, how easy is it to survive in that situation?", "qSentId": 148}, {"answer": "Well, I think common sense would have you think, certainly in the case of this 8-year-old boy, that there is some sort of association here.", "docId": "130826pmt", "aSentId": 177, "question": "Do you believe there is a link?", "qSentId": 176}, {"answer": "Yes, I mean, and I've seen this before.", "docId": "130826pmt", "aSentId": 205, "question": "What do you think of that phenomenon amongst young people these days?", "qSentId": 204}, {"answer": "Well, I still think it goes back to his childhood trauma.", "docId": "130826pmt", "aSentId": 222, "question": "What do you make of it, now that you've had a bit of time to really assess it?", "qSentId": 221}, {"answer": "I completely agree.", "docId": "130826pmt", "aSentId": 234, "question": "Is there enough being done either at the state level or federal level to tackle what many think is the root cause behind so much of the violence?", "qSentId": 233}, {"answer": "Our company is an armor company, full of engineers, and throughout the war and several Darfur contracts we were able to create armor that protected our troops overseas.", "docId": "130826pmt", "aSentId": 272, "question": "So, George Tunis, tell me why you came up with this or why you think it would work?", "qSentId": 271}, {"answer": "We make all levels of armor, so the armor that we've outfitted many school with -- schools with is NIJ Level 3A, so that's exactly the same armor that would be in a police vest.", "docId": "130826pmt", "aSentId": 285, "question": "Can it stop an AR-15 in the hands of somebody like Adam Lanza?", "qSentId": 284}, {"answer": "Yes, I am.", "docId": "130826pmt", "aSentId": 293, "question": "Are you supportive of this?", "qSentId": 292}, {"answer": "It's a great question.", "docId": "130826pmt", "aSentId": 298, "question": "I mean, my argument would be, how does this stop somebody like Adam Lanza with an AR-15 and a hundred bullet magazine, for example?", "qSentId": 297}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130826pmt", "aSentId": 332, "question": "But you're doing more for genuinely bulletproof doors?", "qSentId": 331}, {"answer": "Well, this is -- not -- you know, this is shop (ph) -- we make corporate room ballistic doors out of this.", "docId": "130826pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "And this is the kind of thing you're talking about?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130826pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "ORGAN: Are they -- are they prohibitively (ph) expensive?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "I think so, yes.", "docId": "130826pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "So schools around America could have these relatively cheaply?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "I have two kids in school.", "docId": "130826pmt", "aSentId": 350, "question": "Are you a parent yourself?", "qSentId": 349}, {"answer": "You know, I think kids should be able to go to school in a -- in an environment that is not full of fear.", "docId": "130826pmt", "aSentId": 352, "question": "How do you feel about my just concern about the militarizing of -- of educational process to kids?", "qSentId": 351}, {"answer": "No, this -- this door would not.", "docId": "130826pmt", "aSentId": 363, "question": "And would that door, would that substance stop an AR-15?", "qSentId": 362}, {"answer": "I think at this point, when America says there's a thin red line in the international community, most civilized nations agree with that.", "docId": "130826pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "He's supportive of a military strike against Syria and its regime?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "I didn't say they got the story wrong.", "docId": "130826pmt", "aSentId": 471, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 470}, {"answer": "You know, I actually was hoping to see this movie.", "docId": "130826pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "What is your response to that?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "Ashton Kutcher's impression of Jobs.", "docId": "130826pmt", "aSentId": 529, "question": "Steve jobs?", "qSentId": 528}, {"answer": "Get your (inaudible) feet (ph) out.", "docId": "130826pmt", "aSentId": 539, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 538}, {"answer": "No, I already fired you.", "docId": "130826pmt", "aSentId": 543, "question": "What are you going to do, you're going to fire me?", "qSentId": 542}, {"answer": "There were a lot of incidences of Steve Jobs' history that were like that.", "docId": "130826pmt", "aSentId": 546, "question": "Is that like Steve Jobs?", "qSentId": 545}, {"answer": "I was hoping this movie would be, a, realistic or if not realistic, it's very excited and entertaining.", "docId": "130826pmt", "aSentId": 550, "question": "Are you hoping the Aaron Sorkin (ph) version, the -- the movie that he is bringing out about Steve Jobs will be a little bit more realistic?", "qSentId": 549}, {"answer": "I'm the wrong person to ask.", "docId": "130826pmt", "aSentId": 563, "question": "You haven't flown since 9/11, right?", "qSentId": 562}, {"answer": "It depends.", "docId": "130826pmt", "aSentId": 576, "question": "How many hours of sleep do you need in life, Steve?", "qSentId": 575}, {"answer": "It happened a lot in the old days.", "docId": "130826pmt", "aSentId": 588, "question": "Does that actually happen?", "qSentId": 587}, {"answer": "You know, we had some nice discussions about some of his ideas for a business he sees.", "docId": "130826pmt", "aSentId": 612, "question": "Well, what do and Kanye talk about?", "qSentId": 611}, {"answer": "Yes, Steve Wozniak, one of my favorite guests.", "docId": "130826pmt", "aSentId": 626, "question": "You've got $2 bills?", "qSentId": 625}]